像许多语言一样，Java有两种不同的操作
Like many languages, Java has two different operations
为了测试相等性，这两个操作
for testing equality, and those two operations
有不同的语义。
have different semantics.
在Java中，equals等于运算符
In Java the equals equals operator
比较引用或更准确地说，
compares references or more precisely,
测试引用相等。
a test referential equality.
如果两个引用指向
Two references are equals equals if they point
相同的存储和内存。
to the same storage and memory.
在快照图方面
In terms of snapshot diagrams we've
已绘制两个引用等于
been drawn two references are equals equals
如果它们的箭头指向同一个对象气泡。
if their arrows point to the same object bubble.
equals操作比较对象内容，换句话说
The equals operation compares object contents, in other words
从我们的角度来看
object equality in the sense we've been
在这篇文章里谈论。
talking about in this reading.
必须适当地定义equals操作
The equals operation has to be defined appropriately
对于每个抽象数据类型。
for every abstract data type.
为了便于比较，这里是等式
So for comparison here are the equality the operators
在几种语言中，Java，Objective C，C#，
in several languages, Java, Objective C, C#,
Python和JavaScript。
Python and JavaScript.
引用相等运算符
The referential equality operator
在这些语言中通常等于，
is generally equals equals in these languages,
虽然在Python中，它的关键字是。
although in Python, it's the keyword is.
对象相等操作通常是
The object equality operation is usually
用这些语言调用对象的方法。
a method in these languages that you call in an object.
但不幸的是，在Python中，对象相等运算符
But in Python, unfortunately, the object equality operator
等于等于。
is equals equals.
所以请注意，不幸的是
So notice that equals equals unfortunately
在Java和Python之间转换其含义。
flips its meaning between Java and Python.
如果你做了那可能是个陷阱
That might be a trap if you've done
很多Python程序。
a lot of Python programmings.
别让这迷惑了你。
Don't let that confuse you.
Equals在Java中只测试引用标识。
Equals equals in Java just tests reference identity.
它不会将对象与内容进行比较。
It doesn't compare object to contents.
现在作为这些语言的程序员，
Now as programmers in any of these languages,
我们不能改变指称平等的含义
we can't change the meaning of the referential equality
算符，等于。
operator, equals equals.
在Java中，equals始终表示引用相等。
In Java equals equals always means referential equality.
但是当我们定义一个新的数据类型时，
But when we define a new data type,
我们有责任决定
it's our responsibility to decide
对于数据类型的值，对象相等意味着什么，
what object equality means for values of the data type,
并适当地实现equals方法。
and to implement the equals method appropriately.
所以让我们先考虑一下不可变类型。
So let's think about that for immutable types first.
现在equals方法实际上是
Now the equals method is actually
由对象类定义。
defined by the object class.
它的默认实现如下所示。
And its default implementation looks like this.
它是一个实例方法，接受另一个对象并询问，
It is an instance method that takes another object and asks,
它们的参照物彼此相等吗？
are they referentially equal to each other?
并返回true或false，具体取决于此。
And returns true or false, depending on that.
换句话说，equals方法的默认含义
So in other words, the default meaning of the equals method
实际上与引用相等。
is actually the same as referential equality.
对于不可变的数据类型，这几乎总是错误的。
For immutable data types, this is almost always wrong.
如果您正在编写不可变的数据类型
If you're writing an immutable data type
你必须重写这个equals方法
you have to override this equals method
用你自己的实现替换它。
and replace it with your own implementation.
所以这是我们第一次尝试。
So here's our first try for duration.
我真的想指出
I actually want to point out here
Java中的每个类，即使我们没有编写它
that every class in Java, even though we didn't write that it
扩展对象，它隐式扩展
extends object, it implicitly extends
对象，以便它继承此equals方法，除非
object so that it's inheriting this equals method unless it
覆盖它。
overrides it.
所以这是我们第一次尝试
So here's our first try for duration at overriding
这等于方法。
that equals method.
它说我们要写一个实例方法
It says we're going to write an instance method that
取另一个持续时间，
takes the duration of another duration,
并将此持续时间的长度与该持续时间的
and compares this duration's length with that duration's
长度，并返回true或false，
length, and returns true or false,
取决于它们是否相等。
depending on whether they're equals equals.
所以这里有个微妙的问题。
So there's a subtle problem here.
为什么这不管用？
Now why doesn't this work?
好吧，让我们试试这个代码。
Well let's try this code.
这段代码创建了两个新的duration对象
This code creates two new duration objects
内容相同。
with the same contents in them.
它们都有1分2秒长。
They're both one minute two seconds long.
然后它做了一件有趣的事。
And then it does an interesting thing.
它创建了这个新的object类型的变量
It creates this new variable of type object
称为o2，指向与d2相同的对象。
called o2 that points to the same object as d2.
我们可以这样做，因为所有的持续时间都是隐式的
And we can do this because all durations are implicitly also
对象，因此Java将允许我们指出
objects, so Java will allow us to point
这个o2变量是d2对象。
this o2 variable to d2 object.
然后我们会问，我们会调用equals方法
And then we'll ask, we'll call the equals method
为了测试d1是否等于d2，我们还将
to test whether d1 equals d2, and we'll also
测试d1是否等于o2。
test whether d1 equals o2.
他们应该是平等的，对吧？
And they ought to be equal, right?
如果d1和d2相等，则d1和o2
If d1 and d2 are equal, the d1 and o2
应该相等，因为o2和d2点
ought to be equal because o2 and d2 point
完全相同的地方。
to exactly the same place.
现在我们可以在在线Java教程中看到这段代码的实际操作。
Now we can see this code in action in online Java Tutor.
就在这里。
And here it is.
你看，我们有d1和d2，我们有
You see, we've got d1 and d2, we've
把这两件东西放在记忆里。
got these two objects in memory.
这有点像我们的气泡图和快照图。
Those are kind of like our bubbles and snapshot diagrams.
我们有d1指向每一个，还有o2
And we've got d1 pointing to each of them, and also o2
指向d2指向的同一对象。
pointing to the same object that d2 points to.
但是d1等于d2，这是正确的，它们都有
But d1 equals d2, that does the right thing, they both have
同样的内容，1分2秒，
the same contents, one minute and two seconds,
所以我们想让他们比较平等。
so we want them to compare equals.
但如果我们称d1等于o2，即使2分
But if we call d1 equals against o2, even though 2 points
对于和d2完全相同的物体，我们得到了错误。
to exactly the same object as d2, we're getting false.
那为什么呢？
So why is that?
好吧，原因是
Well, the reason is that it turns out
持续时间实际上重载了equals方法
the duration is actually overloaded the equals method
因为它的方法签名，这部分在这里，
because its method signature, this part right here,
与它正在尝试的不一样
was not identical to the one that it was trying
从对象重写。
to override from the object.
实际上，在持续时间上我们有两种不同的等于方法。
We actually have two different equals methods in duration.
有一个隐式的equals of object方法
There is an implicit equals of object method
是从对象继承的，没有被正确重写，
that was inherited from object, and not correctly overridden,
这个新的等于持续时间。
and this new equals duration.
对吗？
Right?
所以这里的区别是参数的类型是什么。
So the distinction here is what the type of the parameter is.
从一开始我们就看到了超载
Now we've seen overloading since the very beginning
当然是静态检查。
of the course in static checking.
关于重载的一条重要规则
An important rule about overloading
是Java编译器选择
is that the Java compiler selects
在使用编译时的重载操作之间
between overloaded operations using the compile time
参数的类型。
type of the parameters.
例如，当我们使用除法运算符时，
So for example, when we used the division operator,
编译器将选择整数除法
the compiler would choose either integer division
基于参数的浮点除法
of floating point division based on whether the arguments
是整数还是双数。
are ints or doubles.
同样的编译时选择也发生在这里。
Well the same compile time selection happens here.
如果我们传递了一个对象引用，如d1等于o2，
If we passed an object reference, as in d1 equals o2,
我们最终调用equals对象实现
we end up calling the equals object implementation that's
被隐式继承。
been implicitly inherited.
如果我们传递一个d1等于d2的持续时间引用，
If we pass a duration reference as an d1 equals d2,
我们最终调用了equals duration版本。
we end up calling the equals duration version.
即使o2和d2实际上
And this happens even though o2 and d2 actually
在运行时指向同一个对象。
point to the very same object at runtime.
不管怎样，质量已经变得不一致了
Anyway, quality has become inconsistent
因为我们有两个不同的定义
because we have these two different definitions of equals
在不同上下文中调用的。
that are invoked in different contexts.
现在很容易在方法签名中出错
Now it's easy to make a mistake in that method signature
当你打算重写一个方法时，重载它。
and overload a method when you meant to overwrite it.
这是一个常见的错误，Java现在
That's such a common error that Java now
具有语言功能，重写时的注释，
has a language feature, the annotation at override,
把它放在方法声明之前，
which you put before a method declaration,
你应该随时使用它
and you should always use it whenever
您的目的是重写超级类中的方法。
your intention is to override a method in your super class.
当你有相同的符号
And when you have the same notation
Java编译器将检查
the Java compiler will check that there is actually
在超类中具有此签名的方法
a method with this signature in the super-class
给你一个编译器如果你
and give you a compiler if you've made
签名有误。
a mistake in that signature.
所以这里是实现equals方法的正确方法。
So here's the right way to implement that equals method.
我们有at超驰控制系统，
We've got the at override in there,
我们有正确的签名。
we've got the correct signature in there.
现在我们要做一些事情来转动那个物体，
Now we have to do some things in order to turn that object,
我们得到的参数是一个物体，
parameter that we're getting in which is an object,
在一段时间内
into a duration that we can actually
与此持续时间比较。
compare with this duration.
这是用来做这个的样板。
And this is the boilerplate that's used to do that.
它首先要做的是测试对象是否
What it does first is it tests whether the object were being
传入，我们只知道它是静态的资本对象，
passed in, which we only know it as a capital object statically,
我们必须动态测试它是否
we have to test dynamically whether it's actually
持续时间对象。
a duration object.
如果不是的话
And if it's not, the spec for equal
说我们必须返回false因为他们
says that we have to return false because they
无法比较相等。
can't compare equal.
否则，我们要做的就是把这个对象转换成一个持续时间。
Otherwise, what we do is we cast that object into a duration.
我们已经检查过这是安全的，
And we've already checked that that's safe to do,
所以我们现在要引用的是duration类型，
so we'll a reference now that has duration type,
我们可以打电话给GetLength。
and that we can go ahead and call GetLength on.
这确实解决了问题。
And this does fix the problem.
所以现在再说一遍，如果我们像以前那样创造d1，d2和o2，
So now again, if we create d1, d2 and o2 as we did before,
我们问d1是否等于d2，d1是否等于o2，
we ask whether d1 equals d2, and d1 equals o2,
看看这段代码。
and look at this code in action.
我们看到这里也有同样的设施。
We see we have the same set up here.
现在终于o2和d2的行为都是一样的。
Now finally both o2 and d2 are behaving the same way.
顺便说一下，我们在这里引入了一个新的接线员。
So we introduced a new operator here, by the way.
测试运算符的实例
The instance of operator that tests
对象是否为特定类型的实例。
whether an object is an instance of a particular type.
使用的实例是动态类型检查的一个示例，
Using instance of is an example of dynamic type checking,
不是静态类型检查，我们非常喜欢在6005。
not the static type checking that we vastly prefer in 6005.
通常使用面向对象编程的实例
And in general using instance of an object oriented programming
是一种难闻的气味。
is a bad smell.
在6005年，这是我们的另一个规则
In 6005, and this is another of our rules
对于大多数优秀的Java编程来说也是如此。
that holds true for most good Java programming, as well.
这不仅仅是6005的怪癖。
It's not just a 6005 quirk.
的实例在任何地方都不允许
Instance of is disallowed anywhere
除非你必须使用它，
except where you absolutely have to use it,
这就是实现equals的地方。
and that's where that's an implementing equals.
所以如果你在其他地方使用它，
So if you're using it anywhere else,
那你可能做错了什么。
then you're probably doing something wrong.
这项禁令还包括其他方式
And this prohibition also includes other ways
检查对象运行时类型，如调用GetClass。
of inspecting objects runtime types like calling GetClass.
稍后我们将看到一些示例
We'll see some examples later on where you might
尝试使用的实例。
be tempted to use instance of.
我们将在编写备选方案时讨论
And we'll talk about at write alternatives
更安全，更易于改变。
that are safer from bugs and more ready for change.
好的，对象类的规范，
OK, the specification of the object class,
我们所有的类都继承自
the simplistic class that all of our classes inherit from
是如此的重要以至于它经常被称为对象
is so important that it's often referred to as the object
合同。
contract.
合同可以在方法规范中找到
And that contract can be found in the method specifications
对于对象类。
for the object class.
在这里我们要特别关注
And here we're going to focus specifically
关于等价方法的契约。
on the contract for the equals method.
当重写equals方法时
When you override the equals method
你必须遵守它的总合同
you must adhere to its general contract which
相等的状态必须定义一个等价关系
states that equals must define an equivalence relation that
是一个自反的，对称的，传递的关系。
is a relation that reflexive, symmetric, and transitive.
我们一会儿再谈这些是什么意思。
We'll talk about what those mean in a moment.
等于必须一致，所以重复调用
Equals must be consistent, so repeated calls
同一方法必须产生相同的结果
to the same method must yield the same result
没有提供使用equals比较的信息
provided no information using the equals comparisons
对象被修改。
and the object is modified.
所以这就是我们处理可变对象的方法。
So that's how we deal with mutable objects.
但是如果你有一个不可变的对象，
But if you've got an immutable object,
在平等问题上，它必须总是得到同样的结果。
it's got to always yield the same result about equality.
现在这里有一个处理条款
Now there's a clause here for handling
即使我们在6005中没有使用空，
null even though we don't use null in 6005,
或者我们尽量避免，
or we try to avoid it as much as possible,
目标合同中有一条规则
there is a rule in the object contract
说事物不应等同于零。
saying that things should not compare equal to null.
最后，还有另一个方法散列码
And finally, there's this other method hash code
对于两个被认为是
that must return the same result for two objects that are deemed
按等于方法相等。
equal by the equals method.
我们一会儿再谈。
And we'll talk about that in a moment as well.
如果你要去
That's very important if you're going
将类型与内置集合类（如哈希）一起使用
to use your type with built-in collection classes like hash
集合和哈希映射。
sets and hash maps.
所以现在让我们看看当
So now let's see what goes wrong when
我们违反了一些规则，特别是
we break some of these rules, particularly the rules
关于等价关系。
about equivalence relations.
所以我们必须确保有足够的平等定义
So we have to make sure that enough definition of equality
事实上是平等实现的
that's implemented by equals is actually
我们前面定义的等价关系。
an equivalence relation as we defined earlier.
它必须是自反的，必须是对称的
It has to be reflexive, it has to be symmetric
它必须是可传递的。
and it has to be transitive.
如果不是，那么
If it isn't, then the operations that
依赖于相等性，就像内部库操作一样，
depend on equality, like internal library operations,
比如搜索，或者设置数据结构，
like searching, or like set data structures,
会表现得很奇怪。
will behave very strangely.
你不想用数据编程
You don't want to program with a data
有时a引起b但b不等于a的类型。
type in which sometimes a caused b but b doesn't equals a.
对吗？
Right?
这是破坏对称性的一个例子。
That's an example of breaking symmetry.
会导致微妙和非常痛苦的虫子。
Subtle and very painful bugs will result.
这是一个无辜企图的例子
Here's an example of how an innocent attempt
使平等更加灵活可能会出错。
to make equality more flexible can go wrong.
假设我们想在计算上允许一个公差
Suppose we wanted to allow for a tolerance in computing
持续时间[听不见]比较持续时间
duration [INAUDIBLE] comparing duration
对象，因为不同的计算机可能具有
objects because different computers may have
稍微不同步的时钟。
slightly unsynchronized clocks.
所以我们得到了这个时钟SKU常数
So we have this clock SKU constant that
说只要两者有区别
says as long as the difference between the two
长度以秒为单位，只要绝对值
lengths in seconds, as long as the absolute value
其中的差异小于或等于时钟SKU，
of that difference is less than or equal to the clock SKU,
我们要说这两个持续时间是相等的。
we're going to say those two durations are equal.
现在的问题是，哪种财产
Now the question is, which property
等价关系的，自反的，对称的或
of the equivalence relation, reflexive, symmetric or
违反传递性。
transitive is violated.
让我们看下一个练习。
Let's see in the exercise next.